The Gigolo Revelation is a documentary film directed by Ally Wong.
A look at Hong Kong's nightlife, where gigolos service women.
Carlos Armando Ponce Freyre Jr.
(born September 4, 1972) is a Puerto Rican actor,
musician, model, and television personality.
Ponce began his acting career by participating in Spanish
language soap operas for Televisa and Telemundo.
Ponce continued to expand his acting career by
participating in various American television series.
He did not limit himself solely to a career in television.
Ponce, who is also a singer, is also active in the
American movie industry as a character actor.
In film, he played Salvadore in Couples Retreat, Matthew Wright in
Spy and Rodrigo in Deuce Bigalow: European Gigolo.
In television, he played Felix Gonzalez in Cristela, Max Duran in Hollywood
Heights, as well as voicing Santiago Santos in Maya & Miguel.